A Guide to the Spelman Fund of New York records FA063
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Projects, 1925-1970; 4
  - Projects - "1313" Organizations, 4.2
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1934-1949 (Box 43, Folder 535)
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1934-1949 (Box 43, Folder 536)
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1934-1949 (Box 43, Folder 537)
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1934-1949 (Box 43, Folder 538)
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1934-1949 (Box 43, Folder 539)
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1934-1949 (Box 43, Folder 540)
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1934-1949 (Box 43, Folder 541)
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1934-1949 (Box 43, Folder 542)
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1934-1949 (Box 43, Folder 543)
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1934-1949 (Box 43, Folder 544)
    - American Society of Planning Officials - Audits, 1935-1948 (Box 43, Folder 545)
    - American Society of Planning Officials - Audits, 1935-1948 (Box 43, Folder 546)
    - American Society of Planning Officials - Audits, 1935-1948 (Box 43, Folder 547)
    - American Society of Planning Officials - Annual Report, 1937-1945 (Box 44, Folder 548)
    - American Society of Planning Officials - Pamphlets and Reports (Box 44, Folder 549)
    - American Society of Planning Officials - Newsletter, 1935-1949 (Box 44, Folder 550)
    - American Society of Planning Officials - Newsletter, 1935-1949 (Box 44, Folder 551)
    - Civil Service Assembly, 1928-1930 (Box 44, Folder 552)
    - Civil Service Assembly, 1931-1949 (Box 45, Folder 553)
    - Civil Service Assembly, 1931-1949 (Box 45, Folder 554)
    - Civil Service Assembly, 1931-1949 (Box 45, Folder 555)
    - Civil Service Assembly, 1931-1949 (Box 45, Folder 556)
    - Civil Service Assembly, 1931-1949 (Box 45, Folder 557)
    - Civil Service Assembly, 1931-1949 (Box 45, Folder 558)
    - Civil Service Assembly, 1931-1949 (Box 45, Folder 559)
    - Civil Service Assembly, 1931-1949 (Box 45, Folder 560)
    - Civil Service Assembly, 1931-1949 (Box 45, Folder 561)
    - Civil Service Assembly - Audits, 1935-1948 (Box 45, Folder 562)
    - Civil Service Assembly - Audits, 1935-1948 (Box 45, Folder 563)
    - Civil Service Assembly - Audits, 1935-1948 (Box 45, Folder 564)
    - Civil Service Assembly - Annual Report, 1937 (Box 46, Folder 564A)
    - Civil Service Assembly - Annual Report, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 564B)
    - Civil Service Assembly - Annual Report, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 564C)
    - Civil Service Assembly - Annual Report, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 564)
    - Civil Service Assembly - Annual Report, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 564E)
    - Civil Service Assembly - Annual Report, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 564)
    - Civil Service Assembly - Annual Report, 1943 (Box 46, Folder 564G)
    - Civil Service Assembly - Annual Report, 1944 (Box 46, Folder 564H)
    - Civil Service Assembly - Annual Report, 1945 (Box 46, Folder 564I)
    - Civil Service Assembly - Annual Report, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 564J)
    - Civil Service Assembly - Annual Report, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 564K)
    - Civil Service Assembly - Annual Report, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 564L)
    - Civil Service Assembly - Reports (Box 46, Folder 565)
    - Civil Service Assembly - Reports (Box 46, Folder 566)
    - Civil Service Assembly - Reports (Box 47, Folder 567)
    - Civil Service Assembly - Newsletter (Box 47, Folder 568)
    - Council of State Governments, October 1935-1936 (Box 47, Folder 569)
    - Council of State Governments, October 1935-1936 (Box 47, Folder 570)
    - Council of State Governments, October 1935-1936 (Box 47, Folder 571)
    - Council of State Governments, October 1935-1936 (Box 47, Folder 572)
    - Council of State Governments, October 1935-1936 (Box 47, Folder 573)
    - Council of State Governments, October 1935-1936 (Box 47, Folder 574)
    - Council of State Governments, October 1935-1936 (Box 47, Folder 575)
    - Council of State Governments, November 1936-1941 (Box 48, Folder 576)
    - Council of State Governments, November 1936-1941 (Box 48, Folder 577)
    - Council of State Governments, November 1936-1941 (Box 48, Folder 578)
    - Council of State Governments, November 1936-1941 (Box 48, Folder 579)
    - Council of State Governments, November 1936-1941 (Box 48, Folder 580)
    - Council of State Governments, November 1936-1941 (Box 48, Folder 581)
    - Council of State Governments, November 1936-1941 (Box 48, Folder 582)
    - Council of State Governments, November 1936-1941 (Box 48, Folder 583)
    - Council of State Governments, November 1936-1941 (Box 48, Folder 584)
    - Council of State Governments, November 1936-1941 (Box 48, Folder 585)
    - Council of State Governments, November 1936-1941 (Box 48, Folder 586)
    - Council of State Governments, 1942-1949 (Box 49, Folder 587)
    - Council of State Governments, 1942-1949 (Box 49, Folder 588)
    - Council of State Governments - Audits, 1936-1946 (Box 49, Folder 589)
    - Council of State Governments - Audits, 1936-1946 (Box 49, Folder 590)
    - Council of State Governments - Audits, 1936-1946 (Box 49, Folder 591)
    - Council of State Governments - Annual Report, 1935 (Box 49, Folder 591A)
    - Council of State Governments - Annual Report, 1936 (Box 49, Folder 591B)
    - Council of State Governments - Annual Report - Report of Activities, 1936 (Box 49, Folder 591C)
    - Council of State Governments - Annual Report, 1937 (Box 50, Folder 591)
    - Council of State Governments - Annual Report, 1938 (Box 50, Folder 591E)
    - Council of State Governments - Report of the Executive Director to the Board of Managers, 1938 (Box 50, Folder 591)
    - Council of State Governments - Annual Report, 1939 (Box 50, Folder 591G)
    - Council of State Governments - Report of the Executive Director to the Board of Managers, 1939 (Box 50, Folder 591H)
    - Council of State Governments - Annual Report, 1940 (Box 50, Folder 591I)
    - Council of State Governments - Annual Report, 1941 (Box 50, Folder 591J)
    - Council of State Governments - Annual Report, 1942 (Box 50, Folder 591K)
    - Council of State Governments - Annual Report, 1943 (Box 51, Folder 591L)
    - Council of State Governments - Annual Report, 1944 (Box 51, Folder 591M)
    - Council of State Governments - Annual Report, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 591N)
    - Council of State Governments - Annual Report, 1946 (Box 51, Folder 591O)
    - Council of State Governments - Publications (Box 52, Folder 592)
    - Council of State Governments - Publications (Box 52, Folder 593)
    - Council of State Governments - Publications (Box 52, Folder 594)
    - Council of State Governments - Publications (Box 52, Folder 595)
    - Council of State Governments - Publications (Box 52, Folder 596)
    - Council of State Governments - Publications (Box 53, Folder 597)
    - Council of State Governments - Publications (Box 53, Folder 598)
    - Federation of Tax Administrators, 1934-1940 (Box 53, Folder 599)
    - Federation of Tax Administrators, 1934-1940 (Box 53, Folder 600)
    - Federation of Tax Administrators, 1934-1940 (Box 53, Folder 601)
    - Federation of Tax Administrators, 1934-1940 (Box 53, Folder 602)
    - Federation of Tax Administrators, 1941-1949 (Box 54, Folder 603)
    - Federation of Tax Administrators, 1941-1949 (Box 54, Folder 604)
    - Federation of Tax Administrators, 1941-1949 (Box 54, Folder 605)
    - Federation of Tax Administrators, 1941-1949 (Box 54, Folder 606)
    - Federation of Tax Administrators - Audits, 1938-1948 (Box 54, Folder 607)
    - Federation of Tax Administrators - Audits, 1938-1948 (Box 54, Folder 608)
    - Federation of Tax Administrators - Reports (Box 54, Folder 609)
    - Federation of Tax Administrators - Reports (Box 54, Folder 610)
    - Federation of Tax Administrators - Bulletin (Box 54, Folder 611)
    - International City Managers Association, 1928-1949 (Box 55, Folder 612)
    - International City Managers Association, 1928-1949 (Box 55, Folder 613)
    - International City Managers Association, 1928-1949 (Box 55, Folder 614)
    - International City Managers Association, 1928-1949 (Box 55, Folder 615)
    - International City Managers Association, 1928-1949 (Box 55, Folder 616)
    - International City Managers Association, 1928-1949 (Box 55, Folder 617)
    - International City Managers Association, 1928-1949 (Box 55, Folder 618)
    - International City Managers Association, 1928-1949 (Box 55, Folder 619)
    - International City Managers Association, 1928-1949 (Box 55, Folder 620)
    - International City Managers Association, 1928-1949 (Box 55, Folder 621)
    - International City Managers Association, 1928-1949 (Box 55, Folder 622)
    - International City Managers Association, 1928-1949 (Box 55, Folder 623)
    - International City Managers Association, 1928-1949 (Box 55, Folder 624)
    - International City Managers Association - Audits, 1928-1948 (Box 56, Folder 625)
    - International City Managers Association - Audits, 1928-1948 (Box 56, Folder 626)
    - International City Managers Association - Audits, 1928-1948 (Box 56, Folder 627)
    - International City Managers Association - Audits, 1928-1948 (Box 56, Folder 628)
    - International City Managers Association - Annual Reports, 1934-1941 (Box 56, Folder 629)
    - International City Managers Association - Reports (Box 56, Folder 630)
    - International City Managers Association - Publications (Box 56, Folder 631)
    - International City Managers Association - Publication - "Manual of Street Sanitation Records, Including Other Public Works Activities for Cities of 25,000 - 500,000 Population, as Installed in Kenosha, Wisconsin", July 1931 (Box 57, Folder 631A)
    - International City Managers Association - Publication - "Municipal Problems in the Economic Depression", October 1931 (Box 57, Folder 631B)
    - International City Managers Association - Publication - "Some Observations on Municipal Practices in European Cities" by Donald C. Stone and Alice B. Stone, November 1932 (Box 57, Folder 631C)
    - International City Managers Association - Publication - "Organizations and Functions of Municipal Government" (Box 57, Folder 631)
    - International City Managers Association - Bulletins (Box 57, Folder 632)
    - Municipal Financial Officers Association, 1931-1934 (Box 57, Folder 633)
    - Municipal Financial Officers Association, 1931-1934 (Box 57, Folder 634)
    - Municipal Financial Officers Association, 1931-1934 (Box 57, Folder 635)
    - Municipal Financial Officers Association, 1935-1949 (Box 58, Folder 636)
    - Municipal Financial Officers Association, 1935-1949 (Box 58, Folder 637)
    - Municipal Financial Officers Association, 1935-1949 (Box 58, Folder 638)
    - Municipal Financial Officers Association, 1935-1949 (Box 58, Folder 639)
    - Municipal Financial Officers Association, 1935-1949 (Box 58, Folder 640)
    - Municipal Financial Officers Association, 1935-1949 (Box 58, Folder 641)
    - Municipal Financial Officers Association, 1935-1949 (Box 58, Folder 642)
    - Municipal Financial Officers Association, 1935-1949 (Box 58, Folder 643)
    - Municipal Financial Officers Association, 1935-1949 (Box 58, Folder 644)
    - Municipal Financial Officers Association - Audits, 1931-1937 (Box 58, Folder 645)
    - Municipal Financial Officers Association - Audits, 1938-1948 (Box 59, Folder 646)
    - Municipal Financial Officers Association - Audits, 1938-1948 (Box 59, Folder 647)
    - Municipal Financial Officers Association - Reports and Publications (Box 59, Folder 648)
    - Municipal Financial Officers Association - Reports and Publications (Box 59, Folder 649)
    - Municipal Financial Officers Association - Bulletins (Box 60, Folder 650)
    - National Association of Assessing Officers, 1934-1949 (Box 60, Folder 651)
    - National Association of Assessing Officers, 1934-1949 (Box 60, Folder 652)
    - National Association of Assessing Officers, 1934-1949 (Box 60, Folder 653)
    - National Association of Assessing Officers, 1934-1949 (Box 60, Folder 654)
    - National Association of Assessing Officers, 1934-1949 (Box 60, Folder 655)
    - National Association of Assessing Officers, 1934-1949 (Box 60, Folder 656)
    - National Association of Assessing Officers, 1934-1949 (Box 60, Folder 657)
    - National Association of Assessing Officers, 1934-1949 (Box 60, Folder 658)
    - National Association of Assessing Officers - Audits, 1935-1939 (Box 60, Folder 659)
    - National Association of Assessing Officers - Audits, 1940-1948 (Box 61, Folder 660)
    - National Association of Assessing Officers - Audits, 1940-1948 (Box 61, Folder 661)
    - National Association of Assessing Officers - Reports and Publications (Box 61, Folder 662)
    - National Association of Assessing Officers - Reports and Publications (Box 61, Folder 663)
    - National Association of Assessing Officers - Bulletins (Box 61, Folder 664)
    - National Association of Housing Officials, 1933-1938 (Box 61, Folder 665)
    - National Association of Housing Officials, 1933-1938 (Box 61, Folder 666)
    - National Association of Housing Officials, 1933-1938 (Box 61, Folder 667)
    - National Association of Housing Officials, 1933-1938 (Box 61, Folder 668)
    - National Association of Housing Officials, 1939-1949 (Box 62, Folder 669)
    - National Association of Housing Officials, 1939-1949 (Box 62, Folder 670)
    - National Association of Housing Officials, 1939-1949 (Box 62, Folder 671)
    - National Association of Housing Officials, 1939-1949 (Box 62, Folder 672)
    - National Association of Housing Officials, 1939-1949 (Box 62, Folder 673)
    - National Association of Housing Officials, 1939-1949 (Box 62, Folder 674)
    - National Association of Housing Officials, 1939-1949 (Box 62, Folder 675)
    - National Association of Housing Officials - Audits, 1934-1948 (Box 62, Folder 676)
    - National Association of Housing Officials - Audits, 1934-1948 (Box 62, Folder 677)
    - National Association of Housing Officials - Audits, 1934-1948 (Box 62, Folder 678)
    - National Association of Housing Officials - Annual Report, 1934 (Box 62, Folder 679)
    - National Association of Housing Officials - Annual Report, 1936-1947 (Box 63, Folder 680)
    - National Association of Housing Officials - Annual Report, 1936-1947 (Box 63, Folder 681)
    - National Association of Housing Officials - Annual Report, 1936-1947 (Box 63, Folder 682)
    - National Association of Housing Officials - Annual Report, 1936-1947 (Box 63, Folder 683)
    - National Association of Housing Officials - Annual Report, 1936-1947 (Box 63, Folder 684)
    - National Association of Housing Officials - Reports and Publications (Box 64, Folder 685)
    - National Association of Housing Officials - Reports and Publications (Box 64, Folder 686)
    - National Association of Housing Officials - Reports and Publications (Box 64, Folder 687)
    - National Association of Housing Officials - Reports and Publications (Box 64, Folder 688)
    - National Association of Housing Officials - Bulletins (Box 64, Folder 689)
    - National Association of Housing Officials - Bulletins (Box 64, Folder 690)
    - National Association of State Auditors, Comptrollers and Treasurers, 1935-1944 (Box 65, Folder 691)
    - National Association of State Auditors, Comptrollers and Treasurers, 1935-1944 (Box 65, Folder 692)
    - National Association of State Auditors, Comptrollers and Treasurers - Audits, 1938-1943 (Box 65, Folder 693)
    - National Association of State Auditors, Comptrollers and Treasurers - Reports and Publications (Box 65, Folder 694)
    - Public Administration Clearing House, 1930-1938 (Box 65, Folder 695)
    - Public Administration Clearing House, 1930-1938 (Box 65, Folder 696)
    - Public Administration Clearing House, 1930-1938 (Box 65, Folder 697)
    - Public Administration Clearing House, 1930-1938 (Box 65, Folder 698)
    - Public Administration Clearing House, 1930-1938 (Box 65, Folder 699)
    - Public Administration Clearing House, 1930-1938 (Box 65, Folder 700)
    - Public Administration Clearing House, 1930-1938 (Box 65, Folder 701)
    - Public Administration Clearing House, 1930-1938 (Box 65, Folder 702)
    - Public Administration Clearing House, 1939-1947 (Box 66, Folder 703)
    - Public Administration Clearing House, 1939-1947 (Box 66, Folder 704)
    - Public Administration Clearing House, 1939-1947 (Box 66, Folder 705)
    - Public Administration Clearing House, 1939-1947 (Box 66, Folder 706)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Apprentice Training, 1934-1936 (Box 66, Folder 707)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Building, 1934-1947 (Box 66, Folder 708)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Building, 1934-1947 (Box 66, Folder 709)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Paris Round Table Conference, 1933-1935 (Box 66, Folder 710)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Resources Study, 1936-July 1937 (Box 66, Folder 711)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Resources Study, August 1937-1939 (Box 67, Folder 712)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Resources Study, August 1937-1939 (Box 67, Folder 713)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Urban Redevelopment, 1948 (Box 67, Folder 714)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Director's Report (Box 67, Folder 715)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Reports and Publications (Box 67, Folder 716)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Paris Round Table Conference - Reports, 1934 (Box 67, Folder 717)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Resources Study Reports (Box 67, Folder 718)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Audits, 1946-1947 (Box 68, Folder 719)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Audits, 1946-1947 (Box 68, Folder 720)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Annual Report, 1936 (Box 68, Folder 720A)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Annual Report, 1937 (Box 68, Folder 720B)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Annual Report, 1938 (Box 68, Folder 720C)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Appendix of Exhibits for Annual Report, 1938 (Box 68, Folder 720)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Annual Report, 1939 (Box 68, Folder 720E)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Annual Report, 1940 (Box 68, Folder 720)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Annual Report, 1941 (Box 69, Folder 720G)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Annual Report, 1942 (Box 69, Folder 720H)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Annual Report, 1943 (Box 69, Folder 720I)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Annual Report, 1944 (Box 69, Folder 720J)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Annual Report, 1945 (Box 69, Folder 720K)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Annual Report, 1946 (Box 69, Folder 720L)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Report - "Retrospect and Prospect", May 7, 1947 (Box 69, Folder 720M)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Annual Report, 1947 (Box 70, Folder 720N)
    - Public Administration Clearing House - Annual Report, 1948 (Box 70, Folder 720O)
    - Public Administration Service, 1933-1937 (Box 70, Folder 721)
    - Public Administration Service, 1933-1937 (Box 70, Folder 722)
    - Public Administration Service, 1933-1937 (Box 70, Folder 723)
    - Public Administration Service, 1933-1937 (Box 70, Folder 724)
    - Public Administration Service, 1933-1937 (Box 70, Folder 725)
    - Public Administration Service, 1933-1937 (Box 70, Folder 726)
    - Public Administration Service, 1938-1949 (Box 71, Folder 727)
    - Public Administration Service, 1938-1949 (Box 71, Folder 728)
    - Public Administration Service, 1938-1949 (Box 71, Folder 729)
    - Public Administration Service, 1938-1949 (Box 71, Folder 730)
    - Public Administration Service, 1938-1949 (Box 71, Folder 731)
    - Public Administration Service - Audits, 1938-1945 (Box 71, Folder 732)
    - Public Administration Service - Audits, 1938-1945 (Box 71, Folder 733)
    - Public Administration Service - Audits, 1938-1945 (Box 71, Folder 734)
    - Public Administration Service - Annual Report, 1935-1936 (Box 71, Folder 735)
    - Public Administration Service - Annual Report, 1937-1939 (Box 72, Folder 736)
    - Public Administration Service - Reports and Publications (Box 72, Folder 737)
    - 1313 - Comments (Box 72, Folder 738)
    - 1313 - Organization (Box 72, Folder 739)
- General Files, 1922-1945; 5
  This series is arranged alphabetically by organization name.
  This is a non-grant series which includes information on organizations in which The Spelman Fund was directly interested but which it did not support financially. Occasionally there is correspondence in this file relating to a project. For the most part, this series is made up of correspondence.
  - American Association of Port Authorities, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 740)
  - American Institute of Park Executives, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 741)
  - American University, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 742)
  - American Council on Education, 1936-1939 (Box 1, Folder 743)
  - Association of Oregon Counties, 1936-1938 (Box 1, Folder 744)
  - Association of Washington Cities, 1934-1936 (Box 1, Folder 745)
  - Atlanta University, 1928-1929 (Box 1, Folder 746)
  - Brookings Institution, 1929-1935 (Box 1, Folder 747)
  - Brussels Center, 1936-1939 (Box 1, Folder 748)
  - Brussels Center - Reports (Box 1, Folder 749)
  - Canadian National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 750)
  - Carnegie Corporation, 1934-1936 (Box 1, Folder 751)
  - Cincinnati Department of Public Welfare - Employment Demonstration, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 752)
  - Child Guidance Clinic, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 753)
  - Cornell University - Family Research, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 754)
  - Columbia University, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 755)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 756)
  - Federal Council of Personnel Administrators, 1931-1936 (Box 1, Folder 757)
  - Federal-State Relations Service, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 758)
  - Georgia Observational Survey, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 759)
  - Governor's Conference, 1929-June 1930 (Box 2, Folder 760)
  - Governor's Conference, July 1930-1932 (Box 2, Folder 761)
  - Governmental Research Asociates, 1922-1945 (Box 2, Folder 762)
  - Greenville County Council for Community Development, 1935-1938 (Box 2, Folder 763)
  - Griffenhagen and Associates, 1931-1934 (Box 2, Folder 764)
  - Griffenhagen and Associates, 1935-1941 (Box 2, Folder 765)
  - Industrial Relations Counselors, 1929-1935 (Box 2, Folder 766)
  - Institute of Public Administration, 1929-1940 (Box 2, Folder 767)
  - Institute of Public Administration, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 768)
  - International Association of Police Chiefs, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 769)
  - International Federation of Housing and Planning, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 770)
  - Latin American Exploration, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 771)
  - League of Municipalities in the United States and Canada, 1930-1931 (Box 2, Folder 772)
  - Maryland County Survey, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 773)
  - Merriam, Charles, 1928-1929 (Box 3, Folder 774)
  - Moffett, Guy - European Trips, 1932-1937 (Box 3, Folder 775)
  - National Municipal League, 1929-1938 (Box 3, Folder 776)
  - National Municipal League - Reports (Box 3, Folder 777)
  - National Resources Committee, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 778)
  - North Dakota Relief and Debt Survey Commission, 1929-1939 (Box 3, Folder 779)
  - North Dakota Relief and Debt Survey Commission - Reports (Box 3, Folder 780)
  - Pan-American Congress of Municipalities, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 781)
  - Pan-American Congress of Municipalities, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 782)
  - Pan-American Congress of Municipalities, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 783)